Ralph Ellis Search for Tomorrow Collection
Ralph Ellis Search for Tomorrow Collection
1971-1974
Ellis, Ralph (soap opera writer)
7 linear ft.
Scripts, breakdowns, story projections for the daytime television drama Search for Tomorrow.
2534136
Biographical History
Premiering on CBS in 1951, Search for Tomorrow spanned four generations to become the first soap opera to experience long running success. The show is remembered for focusing heavily on family and relationships, and treating such issues as abortion and equal rights for women. The show also launched the acting careers of stars such as Susan Sarandon, Morgan Fairchild, Don Knotts, and Kevin Bacon.
Ralph Ellis was a prolific writer of daytime television dramas. Over the course of a thirty-year career beginning in the 1960s, he worked for all three major networks and was a writer or head-writer for such soap operas as One Life to Live, As the World Turns, General Hospital, Guiding Light, Loving, and Search for Tomorrow.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Ralph Ellis Search for Tomorrow Collection consists of material from Ralph Ellis' work on the serial Search for Tomorrow during the 1970s. The collection is divided into five series. Story projections contains four projected plot outlines, each for six months to a year in advance. 1973 Writers Guild Award material consists of a precis. Accompanying material contains Ralph Ellis' own notes on the collection. These three series are quite small.
The majority of the collection consists of breakdowns and scripts. Breakdowns contains 92 weekly outlines of plot developments. Studio and draft scripts contains 587 scripts for episodes of the series; the majority are studio scripts, some are drafts, and for a few episodes both studio and draft scripts are present. Corresponding four-digit episode numbers are provided for all breakdowns and scripts.
Arrangement of the Collection
All material is arranged by date. Four-digit episode numbers are provided for breakdowns and scripts.
Related Material
has a number of television-related collections. Please refer to for a complete listing
Subject and Genre Headings
Radio, television, film; Popular culture; Ellis, Ralph (soap opera writer); Search for Tomorrow.; Television soap operas.; Television series -- United States.; Outlines.; Scripts (documents); Television writers.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Ralph Ellis.
Inventory
- Story projections
  - Where we stand now, May 8, 1972 (Box 1)
  - Where we stand now, January 8, 1973 (Box 1)
  - Where we stand now, March 26, 1973 (Box 1)
  - Where we stand now, November 26, 1973 (Box 1)
- 1973 Writer's Guild Award
  - Precis for 1973 Writer's Guild Award (Box 1)
- Accompanying material
  - Notes on the Search for Tomorrow material, compiled by Ralph Ellis (Box 1)
- Breakdowns
  - 5059-5063 Breakdowns, Week of February 22, 1971 (Box 1)
  - 5064-5068 Breakdowns, Week of March 1, 1971 (Box 1)
  - 5208-5212 Breakdowns, Week of September 20, 1971 (Box 1)
  - 5213-5216 Breakdowns, Week of September 27, 1971 (Box 1)
  - 5217-5221 Breakdowns, Week of October 4, 1971 (Box 1)
  - 5221-5225 Breakdowns, Week of October 11, 1971 (Box 1)
  - 5226-5230 Breakdowns, Week of October 18, 1971 (Box 1)
  - 5231-5235 Breakdowns, Week of October 25, 1971 (Box 1)
  - 5236-5240 Breakdowns, Week of November 1, 1971 (Box 1)
  - 5241-5245 Breakdowns, Week of November 8, 1971 (Box 1)
  - 5246-5250 Breakdowns, Week of November 15, 1971 (Box 1)
  - 5251-5255 Breakdowns, Week of November 22, 1971 (Box 1)
  - 5255-5259 Breakdowns, Week of November 29, 1971 (Box 1)
  - 5261-5265 Breakdowns, Week of December 6, 1971 (Box 1)
  - 5266-5270 Breakdowns, Week of December 13, 1971 (Box 1)
  - 5271-5275 Breakdowns, Week of December 20, 1971 (Box 1)
  - 5276-5280 Breakdowns, Week of December 27, 1971 (Box 1)
  - 5281-5285 Breakdowns, Week of January 3, 1972 (Box 1)
  - 5286-5290 Breakdowns, Week of January 10, 1972 (Box 1)
  - 5291-5295 Breakdowns, Week of January 17, 1972 (Box 1)
  - 5296-5300 Breakdowns, Week of January 24, 1972 (Box 1)
  - 5301-5305 Breakdowns, Week of January 31, 1972 (Box 1)
  - 5305-5309 Breakdowns, Week of February 7, 1972 (Box 1)
  - 5309-5313 Breakdowns, Week of February 14, 1972 (Box 1)
  - 5314-5318 Breakdowns, Week of February 21, 1972 (Box 1)
  - 5319-5323 Breakdowns, Week of February 28, 1972 (Box 1)
  - 5324-5328 Breakdowns, Week of March 6, 1972 (Box 1)
  - 5329-5332 Breakdowns, Week of March 13, 1972 (Box 1)
  - 5334-5338 Breakdowns, Week of March 20, 1972 (Box 1)
  - 5339-5343 Breakdowns, Week of March 27, 1972 (Box 1)
  - 5349-5353 Breakdowns, Week of April 10, 1972 (Box 1)
  - 5354-5358 Breakdowns, Week of April 17, 1972 (Box 1)
  - 5359-5363 Breakdowns, Week of April 24, 1972 (Box 1)
  - 5364-5368 Breakdowns, Week of May 1, 1972 (Box 1)
  - 5369-5373 Breakdowns, Week of May 8, 1972 (Box 1)
  - 5374-5378 Breakdowns, Week of May 15, 1972 (Box 1)
  - 5379-5383 Breakdowns, Week of May 22, 1972 (Box 1)
  - 5384-5388 Breakdowns, Week of May 29, 1972 (Box 1)
  - 5389-5393 Breakdowns, Week of June 5, 1972 (Box 1)
  - 5394-5398 Breakdowns, Week of June 12, 1972 (Box 1)
  - 5399-5403 Breakdowns, Week of June 19, 1972 (Box 1)
  - 5404-5408 Breakdowns, Week of June 26, 1972 (Box 1)
  - 5409-5413 Breakdowns, Week of July 3, 1972 (Box 1)
  - 5414-5418 Breakdowns, Week of July 10, 1972 (Box 1)
  - 5419-5423 Breakdowns, Week of July 17, 1972 (Box 1)
  - 5424-5428 Breakdowns, Week of July 24, 1972 (Box 1)
  - 5429-5433 Breakdowns, Week of July 31, 1972 (Box 1)
  - 5434-5438 Breakdowns, Week of August 7, 1972 (Box 1)
  - 5439-5443 Breakdowns, Week of August 14, 1972 (Box 1)
  - 5444-5448 Breakdowns, Week of August 21, 1972 (Box 1)
  - 5449-5453 Breakdowns, Week of August 28, 1972 (Box 1)
  - 5454-5458 Breakdowns, Week of September 4, 1972 (Box 1)
  - 5459-5463 Breakdowns, Week of September 11, 1972 (Box 1)
  - 5464-5468 Breakdowns, Week of September 18, 1972 (Box 1)
  - 5469-5473 Breakdowns, Week of September 25, 1972 (Box 1)
  - 5474-5478 Breakdowns, Week of October 2, 1972 (Box 1)
  - 5479-5483 Breakdowns, Week of October 9, 1972 (Box 1)
  - 5484-5488 Breakdowns, Week of October 16, 1972 (Box 1)
  - 5489-5493 Breakdowns, Week of October 23, 1972 (Box 1)
  - 5494-5498 Breakdowns, Week of October 30, 1972 (Box 1)
  - 5499-5503 Breakdowns, Week of November 6, 1972 (Box 1)
  - 5504-5508 Breakdowns, Week of November 13, 1972 (Box 1)
  - 5509-5512 Breakdowns, Week of November 20, 1972 (Box 1)
  - 5513-5517 Breakdowns, Week of November 27, 1972 (Box 1)
  - 5518-5522 Breakdowns, Week of December 4, 1972 (Box 1)
  - 5523-5527 Breakdowns, Week of December 11, 1972 (Box 1)
  - 5528-5532 Breakdowns, Week of December 18, 1972 (Box 1)
  - 5533-5537 Breakdowns, Week of December 25, 1972 (Box 1)
  - 5538-5541 Breakdowns, Week of January 1, 1973 (Box 1)
  - 5542-5546 Breakdowns, Week of January 8, 1973 (Box 1)
  - 5547-5551 Breakdowns, Week of January 15, 1973 (Box 1)
  - 5552-5556 Breakdowns, Week of January 22, 1973 (Box 1)
  - 5557-5561 Breakdowns, Week of January 29, 1973 (Box 1)
  - 5562-5566 Breakdowns, Week of February 5, 1972 (Box 1)
  - 5567-5571 Breakdowns, Week of February 12, 1973 (Box 1)
  - 5572-5576 Breakdowns, Week of February 19, 1973 (Box 1)
  - 5577-5581 Breakdowns, Week of February 26, 1973 (Box 1)
  - 5582-5586 Breakdowns, Week of March 5, 1973 (Box 1)
  - 5587-5591 Breakdowns, Week of March 12, 1973 (Box 1)
  - 5596 Breakdowns (Box 1)
  - 5597-5601 Breakdowns, Week of March 26, 1973 (Box 1)
  - 5602-5606 Breakdowns, Week of April 2, 1973 (Box 1)
  - 5607-5611 Breakdowns, Week of April 9, 1973 (Box 1)
  - 5612-5616 Breakdowns, Week of April 16, 1973 (Box 1)
  - 5698 Breakdowns (Box 1)
  - 5708 Breakdowns (Box 1)
  - 5762-5764 Breakdowns, Week of November 19, 1973 (Box 1)
  - 5765-5769 Breakdowns, Week of November 26, 1973 (Box 1)
  - 5770-5773 Breakdowns, Week of December 3, 1973 (Box 1)
  - 5774-5778 Breakdowns, Week of December 10, 1973 (Box 1)
  - 5779-5783 Breakdowns, Week of December 17, 1973 (Box 1)
  - Notes, Week of April 3, 1973 (Box 1)
- Studio and Draft scripts
  - 5056 Studio Script, 2/17/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5057 Studio Script, 2/18/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5058 Studio Script, 2/19/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5059 Studio Script, 2/22/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5060 Studio Script, 2/23/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5061 Studio Script, 2/24/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5062 Studio Script, 2/25/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5063 Studio Script, 2/26/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5084 Studio Script, 3/30/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5085 Studio Script, 3/31/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5086 Studio Script, 4/1/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5087 Studio Script, 4/2/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5088 Studio Script, 4/5/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5089 Studio Script, 4/6/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5090 Studio Script, 4/7/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5091 Studio Script, 4/8/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5091 Draft Script, 4/8/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5092 Studio Script, 4/9/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5093 Studio Script, 4/12/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5094 Studio Script, 4/13/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5095 Studio Script, 4/14/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5096 Studio Script, 4/15/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5097 Studio Script, 4/16/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5098 Studio Script, 4/19/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5098 Draft Script, 4/19/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5099 Studio Script, 4/20/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5100 Studio Script, 4/21/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5101 Studio Script, 4/22/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5102 Studio Script, 4/23/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5102 Draft Script, 4/23/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5103 Studio Script, 4/26/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5104 Studio Script, 4/27/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5105 Draft Script, 4/28/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5105 Studio Script, 4/28/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5106 Studio Script, 4/29/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5107 Studio Script, 4/30/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5108 Studio Script, 5/3/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5109 Studio Script, 5/4/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5110 Studio Script, 5/5/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5111 Studio Script, 5/6/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5112 Draft Script, 5/7/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5112 Studio Script, 5/7/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5113 Studio Script, 5/10/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5114 Studio Script, 5/11/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5115 Studio Script, 5/12/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5116 Studio Script, 5/13/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5117 Studio Script, 5/14/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5117 Draft Script, 5/14/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5119 Studio Script, 5/18/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5120 Draft Script, 5/19/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5121 Studio Script, 5/20/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5122 Draft Script, 5/21/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5122 Studio Script, 5/21/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5123 Studio Script, 5/24/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5124 Studio Script, 5/25/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5125 Draft Script, 5/26/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5125 Studio Script, 5/26/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5126 Studio Script, 5/27/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5127 Studio Script, 5/28/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5128 Studio Script, 5/31/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5129 Studio Script, 6/1/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5130 Studio Script, 6/2/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5131 Studio Script, 6/3/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5131 Draft Script, 6/3/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5132 Studio Script, 6/4/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5133 Studio Script, 6/7/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5134 Draft Script, 6/8/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5134 Studio Script, 6/8/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5135 Studio Script, 6/9/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5136 Studio Script, 6/10/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5137 Studio Script, 6/11/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5139 Studio Script, 6/15/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5140 Studio Script, 6/16/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5141 Studio Script, 6/17/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5142 Studio Script, 6/18/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5142 Draft Script, 6/18/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5143 Studio Script, 6/21/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5144 Studio Script, 6/22/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5145 Studio Script, 6/23/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5146 Studio Script, 6/24/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5147 Studio Script, 6/25/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5148 Studio Script, 6/28/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5149 Studio Script, 6/29/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5150 Studio Script, 6/30/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5150 Draft Script, 6/30/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5151 Studio Script, 7/1/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5152 Studio Script, 7/2/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5153 Draft Script, 7/5/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5153 Studio Script, 7/5/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5154 Studio Script, 7/6/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5155 Studio Script, 7/7/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5156 Studio Script, 7/8/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5157 Studio Script, 7/9/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5158 Studio Script, 7/12/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5159 Studio Script, 7/13/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5160 Studio Script, 7/14/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5160 Draft Script, 7/14/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5161 Studio Script, 7/15/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5162 Draft Script, 7/16/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5162 Studio Script, 7/16/1971 (Box 2)
  - 5163 Studio Script, 7/19/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5164 Studio Script, 7/20/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5165 Studio Script, 7/21/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5166 Studio Script, 7/22/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5167 Studio Script, 7/23/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5168 Studio Script, 7/26/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5169 Studio Script, 7/27/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5170 Studio Script, 7/28/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5171 Studio Script, 7/29/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5172 Studio Script, 7/30/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5173 Studio Script, 8/2/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5174 Studio Script, 8/3/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5175 Studio Script, 8/4/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5176 Studio Script, 8/5/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5177 Studio Script, 8/6/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5178 Studio Script, 8/9/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5179 Studio Script, 8/10/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5180 Studio Script, 8/11/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5181 Studio Script, 8/12/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5182 Studio Script, 8/13/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5183 Studio Script, 8/16/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5184 Studio Script, 8/17/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5185 Studio Script, 8/18/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5186 Studio Script, 8/19/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5187 Studio Script, 8/20/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5188 Studio Script, 8/23/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5189 Studio Script, 8/24/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5190 Studio Script, 8/25/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5191 Studio Script, 8/26/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5192 Studio Script, 8/27/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5193 Studio Script, 8/30/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5194 Studio Script, 8/31/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5195 Draft Script, 9/1/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5196 Studio Script, 9/3/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5197 Studio Script, 9/6/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5198 Studio Script, 9/7/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5199 Studio Script, 9/8/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5200 Studio Script, 9/9/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5201 Studio Script, 9/10/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5202 Studio Script, 9/13/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5203 Studio Script, 9/14/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5204 Draft Script, 9/15/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5205 Studio Script, 9/16/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5206 Studio Script, 9/17/1971 [?] (Box 3)
  - 5207 Studio Script, 9/27/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5208 Studio Script, 9/22/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5209 Studio Script, 9/23/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5210 Studio Script, 9/24/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5211 Studio Script, 9/27/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5212 Studio Script, 9/28/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5213 Draft Script, 9/29/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5214 Studio Script, 9/30/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5215 Studio Script, 10/1/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5216 Studio Script, 10/4/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5217 Studio Script, 10/5/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5218 Studio Script, 10/6/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5219 Studio Script, 10/7/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5220 Studio Script, 10/8/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5221 Studio Script, 10/11/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5222 Studio Script, 10/12/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5223 Studio Script, 10/13/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5224 Studio Script, 10/14/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5225 Studio Script, 10/15/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5226 Studio Script, 10/18/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5227 Studio Script, 10/19/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5228 Studio Script, 10/20/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5229 Studio Script, 10/21/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5230 Studio Script, 10/22/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5231 Studio Script, 10/25/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5232 Studio Script, 10/26/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5233 Draft Script, 10/27/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5234 Studio Script, 10/28/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5235 Studio Script, 10/29/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5236 Studio Script, 11/1/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5237 Studio Script, 11/2/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5238 Studio Script, 11/3/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5239 Studio Script, 11/4/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5240 Draft Script, 11/5/1971 (Box 3)
  - 5241 Studio Script, 11/8/1971 (Box 4)
  - 5242 Studio Script, 11/9/1971 (Box 4)
  - 5243 Draft Script, 11/10/1971 (Box 4)
  - 5244 Studio Script, 11/11/1971 (Box 4)
  - 5245 Studio Script, 11/12/1971 (Box 4)
  - 5246 Studio Script, 11/15/1971 (Box 4)
  - 5247 Studio Script, 11/16/1971 (Box 4)
  - 5248 Studio Script, 11/17/1971 (Box 4)
  - 5249 Studio Script, 11/18/1971 (Box 4)
  - 5250 Studio Script, 11/19/1971 (Box 4)
  - 5251 Studio Script, 11/22/1971 (Box 4)
  - 5252 Studio Script, 11/23/1971 (Box 4)
  - 5253 Studio Script, 11/24/1971 (Box 4)
  - 5254 Studio Script, 11/25/1971 (Box 4)
  - 5255 Studio Script, 11/26/1971 (Box 4)
  - 5256 Studio Script, 11/29/1971 (Box 4)
  - 5257 Studio Script, 11/30/1971 (Box 4)
  - 5258 Studio Script, 12/1/1971 (Box 4)
  - 5259 Studio Script, 12/2/1971 (Box 4)
  - 5260 Studio Script, 12/3/1971 (Box 4)
  - 5261 Studio Script, 12/6/1971 (Box 4)
  - 5262 Studio Script, 12/7/1971 (Box 4)
  - 5263 Studio Script, 12/8/1971 (Box 4)
  - 5264 Studio Script, 12/9/1971 (Box 4)
  - 5265 Studio Script, 12/10/1971 (Box 4)
  - 5266 Studio Script, 12/13/1971 (Box 4)
  - 5267 Studio Script, 12/14/1971 (Box 4)
  - 5268 Studio Script, 12/15/1971 (Box 4)
  - 5268 Draft Script, 12/15/1971 (Box 4)
  - 5269 Studio Script, 12/16/1971 (Box 4)
  - 5270 Draft Script, 12/17/1971 (Box 4)
  - 5271 Studio Script, 12/20/1971 (Box 4)
  - 5272 Studio Script, 12/21/1971 (Box 4)
  - 5273 Studio Script, 12/22/1971 (Box 4)
  - 5274 Studio Script, 12/23/1971 (Box 4)
  - 5275 Studio Script, 12/24/1971 (Box 4)
  - 5276 Studio Script, 12/27/1971 (Box 4)
  - 5277 Studio Script, 12/28/1971 (Box 4)
  - 5278 Studio Script, 12/29/1971 (Box 4)
  - 5279 Studio Script, 12/30/1971 (Box 4)
  - 5280 Draft Script, 12/31/1971 (Box 4)
  - 5281 Studio Script, 1/3/1972 (Box 4)
  - 5282 Studio Script, 1/4/1972 (Box 4)
  - 5283 Studio Script, 1/5/1972 (Box 4)
  - 5284 Studio Script, 1/6/1971 (Box 4)
  - 5285 Studio Script, 1/7/1972 (Box 4)
  - 5286 Studio Script, 1/10/1972 (Box 4)
  - 5287 Studio Script, 1/11/1972 (Box 4)
  - 5288 Studio Script, 1/12/1972 (Box 4)
  - 5289 Studio Script, 1/13/1972 (Box 4)
  - 5290 Studio Script, 1/14/1972 (Box 4)
  - 5309 Draft Script, 2/14/1972 (Box 4)
  - 5310 Studio Script, 2/15/1972 (Box 4)
  - 5311 Studio Script, 2/16/1972 (Box 4)
  - 5312 Studio Script, 2/17/1972 (Box 4)
  - 5313 Studio Script, 2/18/1972 (Box 4)
  - 5314 Studio Script, 2/21/1972 (Box 4)
  - 5315 Studio Script, 2/22/1972 (Box 4)
  - 5316 Studio Script, 2/23/1972 (Box 4)
  - 5317 Studio Script, 2/24/1972 (Box 4)
  - 5318 Studio Script, 2/25/1972 (Box 4)
  - 5372 Studio Script, 5/11/1972 (Box 4)
  - 5389 Studio Script, 6/5/1972 (Box 4)
  - 5390 Studio Script, 6/6/1972 (Box 4)
  - 5391 Studio Script, 6/7/1972 (Box 4)
  - 5392 Studio Script, 6/8/1972 (Box 4)
  - 5393 Draft Script (partial Script - Act III), 6/7/1972 (Box 4)
  - 5394 Studio Script, 6/12/1972 (Box 4)
  - 5395 Studio Script, 6/13/1972 (Box 4)
  - 5396 Studio Script, 6/14/1972 (Box 4)
  - 5397 Studio Script, 6/15/1972 (Box 4)
  - 5398 Studio Script, 6/16/1972 (Box 4)
  - 5399 Studio Script, 6/19/1972 (Box 4)
  - 5400 Studio Script, 6/20/1972 (Box 4)
  - 5401 Studio Script, 6/21/1972 (Box 4)
  - 5402 Studio Script, 6/22/1972 (Box 4)
  - 5403 Studio Script, 6/23/1972 (Box 4)
  - 5404 Studio Script, 6/26/1972 (Box 4)
  - 5405 Studio Script, 6/27/1972 (Box 4)
  - 5406 Studio Script, 6/28/1972 (Box 4)
  - 5407 Studio Script, 6/29/1972 (Box 4)
  - 5408 Studio Script, 6/30/1972 (Box 4)
  - 5409 Studio Script, 7/3/1972 (Box 4)
  - 5410 Studio Script, 7/4/1972 (Box 4)
  - 5411 Draft Script, 7/5/1972 (Box 4)
  - 5412 Studio Script, 7/6/1972 (Box 4)
  - 5413 Studio Script, 7/7/1972 (Box 4)
  - 5414 Studio Script, 7/10/1972 (Box 4)
  - 5415 Studio Script, 7/11/1972 (Box 4)
  - 5416 Studio Script, 7/12/1972 (Box 4)
  - 5417 Studio Script, 7/13/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5418 Studio Script, 7/14/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5419 Studio Script, 7/17/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5420 Studio Script, 7/18/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5421 Draft Script, 7/19/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5422 Draft Script, 7/20/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5423 Draft Script, 7/21/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5424 Draft Script, 7/24/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5425 Draft Script, 7/25/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5426 Draft Script, 7/26/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5427 Draft Script, 7/27/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5428 Draft Script, 7/28/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5429 Studio Script, 7/31/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5430 Studio Script, 8/1/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5431 Studio Script, 8/2/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5432 Studio Script, 8/3/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5433 Studio Script, 8/4/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5434 Studio Script, 8/7/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5435 Studio Script, 8/8/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5436 Studio Script, 8/9/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5437 Studio Script, 8/10/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5438 Studio Script, 8/11/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5439 Studio Script, 8/14/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5440 Draft Script, 8/15/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5441 Draft Script, 8/16/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5442 Studio Script, 8/17/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5443 Studio Script, 8/18/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5444 Draft Script, 8/21/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5445 Studio Script, 8/22/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5446 Draft Script, 8/23/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5447 Studio Script, 8/24/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5448 Draft Script, 8/25/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5449 Studio Script, 8/28/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5450 Studio Script, 8/29/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5451 Studio Script, 8/30/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5452 Studio Script, 8/31/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5453 Studio Script, 9/1/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5454 Studio Script, 9/4/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5455 Studio Script, 9/5/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5456 Studio Script, 9/6/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5457 Studio Script, 9/7/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5458 Studio Script, 9/8/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5459 Studio Script, 9/11/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5460 Draft Script, 9/12/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5461 Studio Script, 9/13/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5462 Studio Script, 9/14/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5463 Studio Script, 9/15/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5464 Studio Script, 9/18/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5465 Studio Script, 9/19/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5466 Draft Script, 9/20/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5467 Draft Script, 9/21/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5468 Draft Script, 9/22/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5469 Studio Script, 9/25/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5470 Studio Script, 9/26/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5471 Studio Script, 9/27/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5472 Studio Script, 9/28/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5473 Studio Script, 9/29/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5474 Studio Script, 10/2/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5475 Draft Script, 10/3/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5476 Studio Script, 10/4/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5477 Studio Script, 10/5/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5478 Studio Script, 10/6/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5479 Studio Script, 10/9/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5480 Studio Script, 10/10/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5481 Studio Script, 10/11/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5482 Studio Script, 10/12/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5483 Studio Script, 10/13/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5484 Studio Script, 10/16/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5485 Studio Script, 10/17/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5486 Studio Script, 10/18/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5487 Studio Script, 10/19/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5488 Studio Script, 10/20/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5489 Draft Script, 10/23/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5490 Draft Script, 10/24/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5491 Draft Script, 10/25/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5492 Studio Script, 10/26/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5493 Studio Script, 10/27/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5494 Studio Script, 10/30/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5495 Studio Script, 10/31/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5496 Studio Script, 11/1/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5497 Studio Script, 11/2/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5498 Draft Script, 11/3/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5499 Studio Script, 11/6/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5500 Studio Script, 11/7/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5501 Studio Script, 11/8/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5502 Studio Script, 11/9/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5503 Studio Script, 11/10/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5504 Studio Script, 11/13/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5505 Draft Script, 11/14/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5506 Studio Script, 11/15/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5507 Studio Script, 11/16/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5508 Studio Script, 11/17/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5509 Studio Script, 11/20/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5510 Studio Script, 11/21/1972 (Box 5)
  - 5511 Studio Script, 11/22/1972 (Box 6)
  - 5512 Studio Script, 11/24/1972 (Box 6)
  - 5513 Studio Script, 11/27/1972 (Box 6)
  - 5514 Draft Script, 11/28/1972 (Box 6)
  - 5515 Draft Script, 11/29/1972 (Box 6)
  - 5516 Studio Script, 11/30/1972 (Box 6)
  - 5517 Studio Script, 12/1/1972 (Box 6)
  - 5518 Studio Script, 12/4/1972 (Box 6)
  - 5519 Studio Script, 12/5/1972 (Box 6)
  - 5520 Studio Script, 12/6/1972 (Box 6)